Contact

suiying1019@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/alexshin0322 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

FaunaDB ethers.js GSAP

Alex Shin

Full Stack Developer

Brampton, Ontario, Canada

Summary

Senior Web Developer with more than 7 years of rich experience. Feeling interested in web3 projects and other new innovative area. I'm confident to learn any new programming language or skills very quickly and pay attention to details in software development.

Experience

Freelancing

Full Stack Developer

December 2021 - Present (1 year 7 months)

- Full Stack Development: Laravel + Vue/React.
- Frontend Development: ReactJS, Vue 2, 3, Angular
- Web3 Development: Web3.js, Ethers.js, Solidity
- Mobile App Development: React Native, Swift, Kotlin
- Backend Development: Node.js, Python/Jango, PHP, Java

DIGITALAX

Senior Full Stack Engineer April 2021 - June 2022 (1 year 3 months)

Avatar Property & Casualty Insurance

Frontend Developer

June 2020 - December 2021 (1 year 7 months)

- Built an admin pages to manage customer information using React.JS
- Used StyledComponent
- Built Custom Components.
- Used Chart.js to draw various graphs.
- Used GSAP to make fancy animations.

Vogogo

Frontend Developer 2017 - 2018 (1 year)

- Worked on frontend pages for Payment and Risk management pages.

- Integrated with crypto payment.
- Used React.js, Node.js

Education

University of Toronto

Bachelors, Computer Science · (April 2012 - April 2016)